I want to make this very clear that the rise of fascism is an appropriate context to boycott any
influencers, celebrities, people with platforms that refuse to contribute to the people's resistance.
Your rags to riches story is not endearing or unique enough for you to be exempt from the
people's call, from the public call, to use your platform in a time of crisis, to shed light on
important matters, to signpost information and to raise awareness like every single other person
is being expected to do. Nobody's asking influencers or celebrities to lead the revolution,
no one is asking them to get a PhD in political science. What I am trying to remind you all is
that you will all be disposable to the revolution and whatever world comes next because the material
political and social freedoms and needs of the masses around the world will always be more
important than your individualistic careerist ambitions of a content creator. We've got to be
real here, five of the wealthiest people in the whole entire world all own multinational tech and
media companies. So what do you think that means? It means that attention and data are one of the most
powerful currencies in the world, so much so that people are using it to destabilise states,
to restrict human rights, to build and crush empires and you're using it for a vanity project.
And at best you just don't know how high the stakes are right now, so you just can't be trusted with
the platform that you have during this time. But when it's peace time we can reinstate you,
we'll use your discount code, but for now fascism is right here and this digital space is a battlefield and
you are just taking up too much space and resources away from the people and the platforms that are
trying to maximise every avenue to strengthen the people's movement. Remember this, brands do not want
independent thinkers. Tech companies don't want humanitarians. What they want are people so desperate to be the
star of the show that they don't even care about the message of the film that they are starring in.